Finding Aid for the S.A. Griffin collection of underground poetry, Scott Wannberg, and The Carma Bums LSC.2248
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Performance files (Box 114, Box 179, Box 180, Box 181, Box 182, Box 183, Box 184, Box 185, Box 186, Box 187, Box 188, Box 189, Box 190, Box 191, Box 192, Box 194, Box 195, Box 196, Box 197, Box 198, Box 199, Box 200, Box 201, Box 202, Box 203, Box 204, Box 205, Box 206, Box 207, Box 208, Box 209, 
  - Rabbits Over Clevyland materials, 2005, 2006 (Box 190, Folder 5-6, Box 191, Folder 1)
    Box 190, Folder 5: Materials include levyfest programs, Griffin's clevyland calling..., Meat no. 3, d.a. levy and the cleveland scene catalog, levy's roses that (for gene) broadside, a copy of rabbits over clevyland "chicken soup for tessa lowell," a limited edition Rabbits Over Clevyland photo book with photos by Bill Roberts and a DVD-R of Ken Petrochuk's "if i scratch, if i write" levy film.
    Box 190, Folder 6: Print outs of blog posts for the Rabbits Over Clevyland 2006 events produced by S.A. Griffin and Bree Bodnar.
    Box 191, Folder 1: This photo album documents the production of rabbits over clevyland "chicken soup for tessa lowell" created at mac's backs basement, October 29, 2006.
    One DVD-R.
  - Riverwood Poetry Festival programs, 2009 June 24-28 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - S.A. performance flyers (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - S.A. selects..., 2013 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Sal Mimeo..., 2007 (Box 190, Folder 10-11)
  - Sam's Book City flyers, 1996 (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - Santa Cruz Poetry Festival preview, 2012 February 12 (Box 190, Folder 13)
  - Saul White: A Memorial Exhibition program, 2003 (Box 190, Folder 14)
  - Set times (Box 190, Folder 15)
    Set times for a performance which begins with guest host Tequila Mockingbird.
  - Skychurch 2000 press release, 1999 (Box 190, Folder 16)
  - Souvenir programs (Box 190, Folder 17)
  - Tumbleweed Weed In A Box stills (Box 232, Folder 1)
  - Unknown Tour of Words road book, 2006 (Box 232, Folder 2)
    This road book from Griffin's tour with John Dorsey, Ellyn Maybe, and Scott Wannberg includes writing by all and drawings by Scott.
  - Venice West flyers (Box 232, Folder 3)
    This folder contains flyers for To the Beach and Back: Return of the Kid in America, an evening of readings from new books by Griffin, Philomene Long, Frank T. Rios, Tony Scibella, and John Thomas. This event was held at the Sponto Gallery, the site of the old Venice West Cafe.
  - Venice West negatives, 1964 (Box 232, Folder 4)
    One small box contains a black and white negative strip with photos of the Venice West Cafe.
  - Venus in the Badlands photos, 2006 (Box 232, Folder 5)
    Venus In The Badlands, New Mexico photos by OutlawPoetPix.
  - Where Streets Collide materials (Box 232, Folder 6-7)
    Materials include flyers, a program and performer resumes for this theatre piece based upon a one act play "Pigstreet" by Griffin. This piece was directed by Griffin and Peter Flynn and featured Doug Knott, Bobbo Staron, and Griffin.
  - White Trash Apocalypse materials (Box 183, Box 232, Folder 8)
    Box 183: This box contains the White Trash Apocalypse (WTA) road book for Griffin's Words On Wheels tour with Iris Berry and Pleasant Gehman.
    Box 232: This box contains a photographs and a WTA press kit which includes performer bios and photographs for the Words On Wheels tour.
    Iris Berry, Pleasant Gehman, and S.A. Griffin toured the southwestern U.S. as White Trash Apocalypse during October 1995 in Griffin's 1971 Buick Riviera. Iris Berry is a Los Angeles punk progenitor, poet, publisher, and friend of Griffin's. Along with Gehman, Berry lived at the Hollywood punk house Disgraceland and was one of the Ringling Sisters. Griffin officiated at Berry's wedding to Tony Malone. Iris Berry currently operates Punk Hostage Press.
  - Window cards (Box 192, Box 252, Box 260)
    Window cards and lobby posters for theater and dance performances.
  - Woodpussy poster (Box 194, Folder 3)
    One poster from Club Sucker, a Sunday afternoon punk rock beer bust at The Garage on Santa Monica Boulevard hosted by Ms. Vaginal Creme Davis.
  - Words, Well, Spoken: Songs, Too, True program (Box 232, Folder 9)
    This program is for Michael Lane Bruner's night of "West Coast Performance Poetry." In addition to Bruner, performers include Doug Knott, Griffin, Michael M. Mollett, Bobbo Staron, Scott Wannberg, and Laurel Ann Bogen.
  - X posters, undated, 2008 (Box 252, Box 194, Folder 3)
    Box 194: These posters were produced by John E. Miner and Jessee Viduarre's Voxpop Press. Griffin attended these performances as a guest of Diana Bonebrake.
    Box 194: Two silkscreen X posters from the band's shows at the Henry Fonda Theatre in Hollywood.
    Box 252: One 31st Anniversary tour poster (2008).
- Memorabilia (Box 168, Box 191, Box 194, Box 236, Box 245, Box 246, Box 249, Box 252, Box 257, Box 260, Box 262, Box 263, Box 280, Box 281, Box 282, Box 283, Box 284, Box 285, Box 286, Box 287, Box 288, Box 289, Box 290, Box 291, Box 292)
  Memorabilia includes flag remnants from d.a. levy's grave, t-shirts from bookstores and bands, photographs, and memorial programs.
  - Art Detox bag (Box 168, Folder 13)
    One brown paper bag with ART DETOX stencil on it. Images of Griffin using this work may be found in the Poetry Bomb materials.
    Vittore Baroni created these bags for a show in Eagle Rock called pLAyLAnd, where the Poetry Bomb made its first appearance before Griffin began the tour in April 2010.
  - Awards and certificates, 1979-1988, 2007-2011, undated (Box 168, Folder 14, Box 281, Box 282)
    Box 168: Awards for Griffin, Lorraine Perrotta, and Spencer Lane Griffin which include signed certificates from Gloria Molina and Eric Garcetti.
    Box 281: Griffin's K-12 and college certificates of achievement.
    Box 282: Birthday walk certificates signed by Mike M. Mollett and a blank Certificate of Upgrade to Complete Asshole.
  - Stodolsky plaque form, 2011 (Box 168, Folder 15)
    Silicone negative of plaque form designed by Griffin to commemorate Red Stodolsky's Baroque Bookstore located at 1643 North Las Palmas Avenue.
    Sholom "Red" Stodolsky founded and operated Baroque Bookstore aka The University of Red from 1972 until his death in 1998 at the age of 82. Griffin created the plaque in tribute to Red, a major bookman in Hollywood and Los Angeles. According to Griffin, among others, Red's shop was influential and essential for hardcore Bukowski fans, young punkers, poets, and writers.
  - Fireside poet prints (Box 168, Folder 16)
    Portraits of Henry Wadsworth Longfellow and Oliver Wendell Holmes mounted on black cardboard.
  - Wannberg calendar, 2012 (Box 191, Folder 6)
    This Scott Wannberg Memorial and Celebratory Calendar was created by Janet Zarem and includes photos of Scott and copies of his poems. It is dedicated to S.A. Griffin and Lorraine Perrotta, Scott's friends, Scott's tribe, Scott's family, Scott's Guardian Angels.
  - American flag remnants, 2005 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    Four American flags of various sizes and states of disrepair.
    Griffin picked up these flag remnants by d.a. levy's grave on October 29, 2005, levy's birthday. The tattered flag was used as original art for the cover of Sometimes City undercovers which Griffin created at the 2005 Levyfest in Cleveland, Ohio. Griffin used the intact flag to create center piece art.
  - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 10, Box 281, Box 282)
    Box 194: This color photograph of an "ON WORD" California personalized license plate was a gift from Bowerbird Intelligentleman aka Bruce Morasch.
    Box 281: Photographs include Griffin's father; S.A. and Lorraine Perrotta at Linda Bukowski's house with cat Sutra; the Al's Bar urinals by Gary Leonard; Leonard's portrait of Sammy Davis Jr. in Beverly Hills; a signed black and white promotional glossy of Alex Trebek; Charles Bukowski's grave site; Tony Scibella, Gayle Davis, Michelle White, Ed Ward, and Griffin at the Mercury Cafe; Sahid's trip to Catalina; and his Onyx farewell party. Photographs also include a trip to San Francisco, photographs of Scott Wannberg, Ike's farewell, Spencer Griffin's college graduation, Griffin's face paint, negatives of Griffin's apartment, Scott's birthday party, Griffin and Tony Scibella at the Cannabis Cup in Amsterdam, Griffin's trip to the Marilyn Monroe Theatre in San Francisco, Tony Scibella's memorial, and apartment photographs.
    Box 282: Photographs include S.A. and Lorraine Perrotta by Mike M. Mollett, Michelle White and Steve Wilson by Marcia Ward, Robin Griffin by Sandy Pimperton, and S.A. with Allen Ginsberg.
    Box 281: One CD-R.
  - S.A. Griffin Water print, 1985 (Box 236)
    One large framed black and white print for part of a postcard series created for the Water Espresso Gallery, formerly at the corner of Santa Monica and Hudson. Griffin hand wrote a piece of his longer poem "Pigstreet" on this print.
    Griffin was a regular at The Water beginning with the Wednesday night poetry open, the first place he ever read publicly in L.A. (1981-1982) This is where Griffin met Mike Bruner and Bobbo Staron. Bruner would become a founding member of The Lost Tribe and The Carma Bums, Staron a founding member of The Carma Bums. The Water was owned by artist Frederick Sauls who owned the entire building which included The Lhasa Club and Figtree Theatre.
  - LACMA Berlin Wall piece, 2009 November (Box 245)
    This box contains a piece of the Los Angeles County Museum of Art (LACMA) "Berlin Wall" from the 20th anniversary of the fall of the Berlin Wall.
    According to Griffin, at one point during the exhibition, against the wishes of the museum, the crowd executed a successful art rebellion to "tear down that wall." This piece exists as a remnant from this action.
  - Woodstock plaque, 1994 (Box 246, Folder 1)
    One limited edition commemorative plaque from the 25th Anniversary of the music festival. Framed memorabilia includes a silver medallion, a ticket, and a VIP laminate.
  - Liberace bag (Box 249)
    One white vinyl bag with zipper and golden Liberace signature piano logo. The right hand corner reads: Hansen House, Hollywood 1515 N. Vine Street/Hollywood, Calif. 90028.
    This bag was gifted to Griffin by Karl Ellis who was working for Barry Manilow at the time. Ellis was an actor/artist who made money working as an assistant and artist for Barry Manilow in the late 1970s and early 1980s. Ellis created a logo that Manilow used on one of his albums. Ellis lived with his older lover, Jack Pierce, an actor and director. Early on during the epidemic, Ellis passed away from AIDS.
  - On the Road scroll poster (Box 257)
    Poster of Jack Kerouac's On The Road scroll.
  - Lobby cards, 2005-2006 (Box 260)
    One Skylight Books Mourning Becomes Electric promotional lobby card signed with drawings by both Bruce Wagner and James Ellroy for their book tour during which they read from each other's work (2006) and one Skylight Books promotional lobby card for Pam Tent's book tour about her life as a "Fabulous Cockette" (2005).
  - S.A. Griffin birthday posters (Box 262)
    This box contains two posters for Griffin's birthdays as well as posters for the Los Angeles 1984 Olympics and the Los Angeles International Film Exposition 10th Anniversary.
  - Music posters (Box 194, Folder 7, Box 252, Box 263, Box 281)
    Box 194: One black and white poster of Richie Havens, signed by Havens, one of Griffin's favorite singer/songwriters.
    Box 252: One full color Spring Awakening cast poster signed by all from a performance at the Pantages Theatre where Griffin took his son Spencer for his 20th birthday.
    Box 263: Punk, rock, and metal posters include the following: The Minutemen, The Cramps, Sonic Youth, Rocky Horror, Girlschool, Hanoi Rocks, The Clash, The Sex Pistols, and a Rolling Stones promo for a Germany gig that never happened.
    Box 281: Hollywood Poseur poster featuring punk rock fashion such as extra skinny ties, tite black jeans, knife earrings, wraparound sunglasses, bondage straps, band buttons, studs, spikes, and wristbands.
  - Arm cast, circa 1999 (Box 280)
    Fake arm cast from a benefit organized by Johnette Napolitano for Pleasant Gehman at the Whiskey a Go Go. The cast is signed by all performers including Napolitano, members of Concrete Blonde, and Possum Dixon.
  - U.S.A.F. book (Box 281)
    One United States Air Force Basic Military Training graduation book signed by Griffin's fellow trainees.
  - Ephemera (Box 281, Box 282)
    Box 281: Business cards, postcards, and name cards include those of Reverend S.A. Griffin of Dynasty of Divine Love and Tolerance, Reverend Mike Cronin, a Ken Kesey calling, Reserved for Arthur Saxon, Metro Poet, Zamorano Club Guest, Stop Nuclear Weapons Testing Now!, and a vintage How Am I Doing?
    This box also contains the following: No Vote Left Behind Kerry/Edwards 2004 bumper sticker created by Griffin, a Kill Radio sticker, and a color photocopy of Jon Howard's Beat American flag guitar rag signed by Abbie Hoffman, Allen Ginsberg, and William S. Burroughs.
    Box 282: Hunter S. Thompson Fear and Loathing in America coasters, James Weldon Johnson USPS postcard, BillyBobaPalooza name badges, The Moment bumper sticker, a black X arm band from an L.A. gig, protest flyers, d.a. levy rabbits over clevyland coasters, a piece of the Dalai Lama's mandala, an Angry Thoreauan Magazine syringe, and a Museum of Death membership brochure.
  - Memorial programs (Box 281, Box 282)
    Box 281: Programs for the following: Frank O'Hara, Kenneth Patchen, and Larry Lake.
    Box 282: Programs for the following: Saul White, Tony Scibella, Michael Montfort, Philomene Long, and Lawrence Chandler Leigh. Included with the Tony Scibella memorial card are photographs from Tony Scibella's memorial.
  - Astro-Forecast, 2000-2001 (Box 282)
    A bound astrology forecast for Griffin by Rockie Horoscope.
  - Mousepad (Box 282)
    One "I Choose Not To Believe In War Holy Or Not" mousepad.
  - Medical marijuana documents (Box 282)
    Medical marijuana documentation includes letters of recommendation from attending physicians for Griffin's use of cannabis for medical purposes and Griffin's verification card.
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 283, Box 284, Box 285)
    THE FOLLOWING BOXES CONTAIN AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. To review these audiovisual materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
    Box 283: Fourteen VHS tapes.
    Box 284: Eight VHS tapes, 4 Hi-8 video tapes, and 2 audio cassettes.
    Box 285: Twelve audio cassettes, 6 DVDs, and 1 CD-R.
    Box 331: Three VHS tapes.
    Box 283: Titles include Visiting...With Huell Howser, Things That Aren't Here Anymore, Frank Lloyd Wright Fallingwater: A Conversation With Edgar Kaufmann, Jr., Popdefect Live With This (Adrift In America), The Henry Miller Odyssey, and Zimmerman & Markman MoveOn.org Debate.
    Box 284: Titles include Aunt Nellie's 90th Family Reunion, Paiz Video Memories, Happy 40th, Spencer's 6th B-day, Spencer's 7th B-day, Teddy the Kitty, and Classic Beverly Hills Auto Tour.
    Box 285: Titles include Father's Day Speech, Sesame Street Songs, Dad #1, Fully Awake: Black Mountain College, i (heart) huckabees, Memories of Scott, Tanka: An Animated Vision of The Tibetan Book of the Dead, and Audio Shoes.
    Box 331: Titles include Cousin S.A. Griffin's 50th Birthday Bash and Steve and Lorraine's Wedding.
  - T-shirts (Box 286, Box 287, Box 288, Box 289, Box 290, Box 291, Box 292)
    Box 286: Pale Rider, Cool As Ice, Beyond Baroque, The Other Side, Space Ark Gallery, and the Onyx.
    Box 287: SAG, Celebrity Jeopardy!, Perry Mason, Candide, and Monsters.
    Box 288: The Ringling Sisters, Born To Be Bad, Santa Cruz Poetry Festival, The Lummox Journal, Ken Kesey, The 1996 Carma Bums Twisted Tour of Words, The 1991 Carma Bums Start From Zero Secret Tour of Words, and The Carma Bums 1992 Lost Tour of Words.
    Box 289: University High School Coffeehouse/Poetry Reading, Writings on the Wall: Spoken Word Festival, Word Avenue 50 Studio, 4 Words Written Spoken, Sparring With Beatnik Ghosts, Next...The Guide To SoCal Word Art Events, Save the Books, and The Carma Bums Start From Zero Secret Tour of Words 1991.
    Box 290: AFTRA, National Lampoon's Joy of Sex, Mambo! Films, Insomnia, 2010: A Beyond Baroque Odyssey, Festival of Masks, LACC 1992 Readathon, and The Ringling Sisters.
    Box 291: Bukowski, Tribe, Beat-L, Vesuvio Cafe, Jack Brewer and Bazooka, Team Bukowski Black Sparrow Press, Downtown Lives! 1997, I'd Rather Be Reading Bukowski, and WWC.
    Box 292: The Onyx Cafe, LACC Readathon 1990, 666 Princess of Hollywood, Kblt, No Fucking Way, White Trash Apocalypse, I Rocked With KLOS, Damaged Goods, Rip Griffin's, and Morrison.
- Acting career materials (Box 168, Box 194, Box 211, Box 212, Box 213, Box 214, Box 215, Box 216, Box 217, Box 218, Box 219, Box 220, Box 221, Box 222, Box 223, Box 224, Box 225, Box 226, Box 227, Box 228, Box 229, Box 230, Box 231, Box 245, Box 256, Box 262)
  Materials related to Griffin's acting career, which are organized chronologically, include materials on the Act Fast 5 strike, programs, photographs, contracts, press kits, clippings, scripts, posters, resumes, and audiovisual recordings.
  - Files, circa 1970s-2014 (Box 194, Folder 8, Box 168, Folder 3-4, Box 211, Box 212, Box 213, Box 214, Box 215, Box 216, Box 217, Box 218, Box 245, Box 256, Box 262)
    Box 217: Seven CDs of Griffin's headshots.
    Box 245: Glenn Dubose is Griffin's acting mentor and friend. Dubose was one of Griffin's teachers at Chabot College, Hayward, California (1976-1978). Griffin worked as Dubose's assistant during his second year at Chabot. Dubose directed Griffin in The Birds (Hoopoe), Gypsy (Cigar), and Candide (Candide).
    Box 168: Folder 3 contains two copies of The Chronicle which publicizes the musical Innocents Abroad. Folder 4 contains a black and white photo of Griffin with Tamara Morgan during a rehearsal for The Physicists at Chabot College, Hayward. Morgan played Nurse Monika and Griffin, Mobius.
    Box 194: Posters for productions in which Griffin performed include Ladies In Retirement, Guys & Dolls, and Fiddler On The Roof.
    Box 211: This box contains scripts, programs, clippings, binders of Griffin's work at Chabot College, and photographs of Griffin in Fiddler On The Roof and Guys & Dolls at Macon Little Theatre.
    Box 212: This box contains contracts, programs and scripts such as No Scratch, Medea, Dying For It, and Innocents Abroad.
    Box 213: This box contains Pale Rider and Let It Ride press kits, acting contracts, royalty records, and clippings.
    Box 214: This box contains acting resumes and scripts for Alien Nation, Baywatch, Matlock, Red River Rats, Cool As Ice, and Secrets of the Luxor Pyramid "Timestorm." The Luxor files include a press kit, wrap party photos and ephemera, a Douglas Trumbull bio, and a black and white photo of Griffin on set which is signed by Trumbull. This box also contains photographs and a drawing of Griffin on the set of The Korean War in China and a poem Griffin wrote for the directors, cast and crew.
    Box 215: This box contains an album of photographs from September-November 2000 when Griffin was the part of the first group of SAG actors to work in China for the China Central Television (CCTV) series The Korean War in which Griffin portrayed General Matthew B. Ridgway.
    Box 216: This box contains correspondence, photos, scrapbooks and press releases related to Act Fast 5, a rank and file grass roots movement of working actors who conducted a rolling fast as a protest against the Association of National Advertisers (ANA) and the Association of American Advertising Agencies (AAAA). The action began on August 1, 2000 and included the following members: James Arone, S.A. Griffin, Peaches Johnson, Raymond O'Connor, and Jerri Zucchi.
    Box 217: This box contains digital head shots; Euphrates scripts; and a Writers Guild of America, West Inc. certificate of registration for Griffin's American Garbage Head screenplay.
    Box 218: This box contains scripts, flyers, copies of Griffin's filmographies, photographs from various productions such as Griffin as Marvin Gardens from Alien Nation, and headshots.
    Box 245: Two mounted photographs of Griffin from Chabot College performances directed by Glenn Dubose. The first is Griffin as Candide and the second is Griffin as Hoopoe, King of the Birds in Aristophanes' The Birds (1977-1978).
    Box 252: Mounted black and white photograph of Griffin as a bank robber in a short film early in his career (1985).
    Box 256: One black and white ride film trilogy storyboard for the Luxor Hotel in Las Vegas, inscribed to Griffin by Director Douglas Trumbull (1993 February). This box also contains an Associated Chabot Thespians poster for Lovers and Other Strangers.
    Box 262: Film posters from Griffin's career include the following: Cool As Ice, No More Baths, Red Velvet, and Vegas Vacation.
  - Audiovisual materials (Box 219, Box 220, Box 221, Box 222, Box 223, Box 224, Box 225, Box 226, Box 227, Box 228, Box 229, Box 230, Box 231)
    Box 219: Fourteen VHS tapes.
    Box 220: Six U-matic tapes and two VHS tapes.
    Box 221: Six U-matic tapes and one VHS tape.
    Box 222: Eleven audio cassettes, three VHS tapes, one DVD and one 8-track cassette tape.
    Box 223: Thirteen VHS tapes.
    Box 224: Fourteen VHS tapes.
    Box 225: Thirteen VHS tapes.
    Box 226: Fourteen VHS tapes.
    Box 227: Fourteen VHS tapes.
    Box 228: Nine DVDs, four VHS tapes and two U-matic tapes.
    Box 229: Thirteen VHS tapes and one 8 mm video tape.
    Box 230: Six 16 mm film reels, five Betamax tapes, and one VHS tape.
    Box 231: Five 8 mm film reels and four 16 mm film reels.
    Box 219-220: Tapes include Let It Ride, Matlock, Designing Women, and Twins.
    Box 221-222: Tapes include Alcohol Awareness, Apple Thematic Campaign "Going to Work," Black Coffee, and radio spots.
    Box 223-224: Tapes include Perry Mason, Take Willy With 'Ya, Schwepps 2000, Deadly Care, Melrose Place, and acting class.
    Box 225-226: Tapes include commercials, Father Dowling Mysteries, and Las Vegas.
    Box 227-228: Materials include Days of Our Lives, Matlock, Air, Act Fast 5 Screen Actors Guild, Innocents Abroad, Play Date, and Luxor.
    Box 229-231: Tapes include No More Baths!, Pale Rider, S.A. Griffin Promo, Twins, Cool As Ice, Luxor, and Act Fast 5 Strike 2000.
- Artwork (Box 114, Box 168, Box 191, Box 193, Box 194, Box 233, Box 234, Box 235, Box 236, Box 237, Box 238, Box 239, Box 240, Box 241, Box 242, Box 243, Box 244, Box 245, Box 246, Box 247, Box 248, Box 249, Box 250, Box 251, Box 252, Box 254, Box 255, Box 256, Box 257, Box 258, Box 259, Box 260, Box 261, Box 262, Box 264, Box 265, Box 266, Box 267, Box 268, Box 269, Box 270, Box 271, Box 272, Box 273, Box 274, Box 275, Box 276, Box 277, Box 278, Box 279)
  Griffin's art collection, which is organized alphabetically by last name, features art in the form of collages, drawings, paintings, mail art, mixed media, and other formats by Griffin, Tony Scibella, Mark Cheka, Frank T. Rios, Charles Bukowski, Earl Newman, Aida Cynthia DeSantis, Tomata du Plenty, Steve Wilson, and other artists.
  - Ajamian, Edward, 1980s (Box 258)
    This framed black and white photograph of the Brooklyn Bridge was a gift to Griffin from his friend, a regular at the Onyx.
  - Arno, Van, 1993 July (Box 268)
    One framed painting of a tribal sacrifice.
    Arno was a friend of Griffin and a regular at the Onyx.
  - Ausgang, Anthony, late 1990s (Box 114, Folder 7, Box 240)
    Ausgang was a good friend of Griffin and one of the Onyx Cafe regulars.
    Box 114: Limited edition signed full color print.